MALEEK A. ADEBARE @TECHFTABDUL ON X

FRONT-END DEVELOPER | CONTENT WRITER | GRAPHICS DESIGNER | SALES & DIGITAL MARKETER



- +974 3047 8599
- ✓ solelyabdul@gmail.com
- Q Doha, Qatar
- techftabdul.github.io

PROFILE

I'm techftabdul on X a proficient front end developer, graphics designer and technical writer with over 2 years of experience. I design user friendly graphics, develop mobile friendly websites and write self explanatory threads and documentation on DeFi, Web Dev and Crypto. I'm passionate about helping valuable brands solve problems with tech.

SKILLS

- Web Design
- Technical Writing
- Digital Marketing
- Front End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- Creative Design & Branding
- Algorithm Thinking

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WEB DEV & GRAPHICS DESIGNER

2022 - Till Date

- Developed creative designs for branding.
- Coding in various front-end development libraries.
- Developed static & portfolio website for businesses and brands.

SOCIAL MEDIA CONTENT MANAGER

2019-Till Date

- Developed interactive social media contents on Instagram & Twitter.
- Created social media campaigns & advertisement that promoted engagements and boosted online presence on the web.
- Interacted with multiple clients and potential customers online to facilitate engagement and interactions online.
- Wrote self explanatory threads and documentation on web developmen, marketing and DeFi

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Air Force Secondary School Lagos 2007 - 2013

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

University of Ilorin, Nigeria 2013-2018